Guide to the Richard Charles Lee Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Mayoral Files, 1943-1969; Series I; 44 linear feet (106 boxes)
  - 1965
    - Johnson, Lyndon B. (Box 73, Folder 1378)
    - "K" general (Box 73, Folder 1379)
    - "L" general (Box 73, Folder 1380-1381)
    - Library (Box 73, Folder 1382)
    - "Mac" general (Box 73, Folder 1383)
    - "M" general (Box 73, Folder 1384-1385)
    - Montano, George J. (Box 73, Folder 1386)
    - "N" general (Box 73, Folder 1387)
    - "O" general (Box 74, Folder 1388)
    - "P" general (Box 74, Folder 1389)
    - Park Department (Box 74, Folder 1390-1391)
    - Personnel (Box 74, Folder 1392)
    - Public Works Department (Box 74, Folder 1393)
    - Purchasing Department (Box 74, Folder 1394)
    - "Q" general (Box 74, Folder 1395)
    - "R" general (Box 74, Folder 1396)
    - Redevelopment: Adams, Melvin J. (Box 74, Folder 1397-1400)
    - Redevelopment: Appleby, L. Thomas (Box 75, Folder 1401)
    - Redevelopment: Church Street (South) (Box 75, Folder 1402)
    - Redevelopment: Cogen, Joel (Box 75, Folder 1403)
    - Redevelopment: Coliseum (Box 75, Folder 1404)
    - Redevelopment: Dixwell Project (Box 75, Folder 1405)
    - Project Redevelopment: Front Block (Box 75, Folder 1406-1407)
    - Redevelopment: Hanas, Joanna D. (Box 75, Folder 1408)
    - Redevelopment: Long Wharf (Box 75, Folder 1409)
    - Redevelopment: Macy's (Box 75, Folder 1410)
    - Redevelopment: miscellaneous (Box 75, Folder 1411-1412)
    - Redevelopment: Shannon, Chuck (Box 75, Folder 1413)
    - Redevelopment: State Street (Box 75, Folder 1414)
    - Redevelopment: Wooster Square (Box 75, Folder 1415)
    - Redinger, Joyce (Box 75, Folder 1416)
    - "S" general (Sa-Si) (Box 75, Folder 1417)
    - "S" general (Sk-Sw) (Box 76, Folder 1418)
    - Shriver, R. Sargent (Box 76, Folder 1419)
    - Southern Connecticut State College (Box 76, Folder 1420)
    - "T" general (Box 76, Folder 1421)
    - Talbot, Allan (Box 76, Folder 1422)
    - Tax Office (Box 76, Folder 1423)
    - Traffic and Parking, Department of (Box 76, Folder 1424-1425)
    - "U" general (Box 76, Folder 1426)
    - Unions (Box 76, Folder 1427)
    - "V" general (Box 76, Folder 1428)
    - "W" general (Box 76, Folder 1429)
    - Welfare, Department of (Box 76, Folder 1430)
    - Wolfinger, Raymond (Box 76, Folder 1431)
    - "XYZ" general (Box 76, Folder 1432)
    - Yale University (Box 76, Folder 1433-1435)
  - 1966
    - "A" general (Box 77, Folder 1436)
    - Administration (Box 77, Folder 1437)
    - Airport (Box 77, Folder 1438)
    - Assessors, Board of (Box 77, Folder 1439)
    - "B" general (Box 77, Folder 1440-1444)
    - Brewster estate (Box 77, Folder 1445)
    - Building Department (Box 77, Folder 1446)
    - "C" general (Ca-Cl) (Box 77, Folder 1447)
    - "C" general (Co-Cu) (Box 78, Folder 1448)
    - Charter Revision Committee: public hearing (Box 78, Folder 1449)
    - Citizens Action Commission (Box 78, Folder 1450)
    - Cleveland: an invitation to (Box 78, Folder 1451)
    - Community Progress, Inc. (Box 78, Folder 1452)
    - Connecticut, State of: general (Box 78, Folder 1453)
    - Connecticut, State of: Highway Department (Box 78, Folder 1454)
    - Connecticut, State of: Highway Department Route 34, Interstate 91 (Box 78, Folder 1455)
    - Controller (Box 78, Folder 1456)
    - Corporation Counsel (Box 78, Folder 1457)
    - "D" general (Box 79, Folder 1458-1459)
    - Democratic Party (Box 79, Folder 1460)
    - Dempsey, John N. (Box 79, Folder 1461)
    - "E" general (Box 79, Folder 1462)
    - Education, Department of (Box 79, Folder 1463-1465)
    - Engineering Department (Box 79, Folder 1466)
    - "F" general (Fa-Fi) (Box 79, Folder 1467)
    - "F" general (Fl-Fu) (Box 80, Folder 1468)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 80, Folder 1469)
    - "G" general (Box 80, Folder 1470-1473)
    - Golden, John M. (Box 80, Folder 1474)
    - "H" general (Box 80, Folder 1475-1477)
    - Health, Department of (Box 80, Folder 1478)
    - Housing Authority (Box 80, Folder 1479)
    - Housing Authority (Box 81, Folder 1480)
    - Housing and Home Finance Agency (Box 81, Folder 1481)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Department of: Robert Weaver (Box 81, Folder 1482)
    - "I" general (Box 81, Folder 1483)
    - "J" general (Box 81, Folder 1484)
    - "K" general (Box 81, Folder 1485-1486)
    - "L" general (Box 81, Folder 1487-1489)
    - Lead poisoning (Box 81, Folder 1490)
    - Library (Box 81, Folder 1491)
    - "Mac" general (Box 81, Folder 1492)
    - "M" general (Box 82, Folder 1493-1495)
    - Montamo, George J. (Box 82, Folder 1496)
    - "N" general (Box 82, Folder 1497)
    - New Haven Foundation (Box 82, Folder 1498)
    - "O" general (Box 82, Folder 1499)
    - "P" general (Box 82, Folder 1500-1501)
    - Park Department (Box 82, Folder 1502)
    - Personnel (Box 82, Folder 1503)
    - Police Department (Box 82, Folder 1504)
    - Public Works (Box 83, Folder 1505)
    - "Q" general (Box 83, Folder 1506)
    - "R" general (Box 83, Folder 1507-1508)
    - Redevelopment: Adams, Melvin J. (Box 83, Folder 1509-1510)
    - Redevelopment: Armstrong Rubber Company (Box 83, Folder 1511)
    - Redevelopment: Coliseum (Box 83, Folder 1512)
    - Redevelopment: Dixwell Project (Box 83, Folder 1513)
    - Redevelopment: Federal Building, Post Office and Government Center (Box 83, Folder 1514)
    - Redevelopment: Front Block (Box 83, Folder 1515)
    - Redevelopment: Hill (Box 83, Folder 1516)
    - Redevelopment: Knights of Columbus (Box 83, Folder 1517)
    - Redevelopment: Long Wharf (Box 83, Folder 1518)
    - Redevelopment: miscellaneous (Box 83, Folder 1519-1520)
    - Redevelopment: railroad (Box 83, Folder 1521)
    - Redevelopment: Sears, Roebuck and Company (Box 83, Folder 1522)
    - Redevelopment: State Street (Box 83, Folder 1523)
    - Ribicoff, Abraham A. (Box 84, Folder 1524)
    - "S" general (Box 84, Folder 1525-1527)
    - Second National Bank (Box 84, Folder 1528)
    - Shriver, Sargent (Box 84, Folder 1529)
    - "T" general (Box 84, Folder 1530)
    - Telegrams (Box 84, Folder 1531)
    - Traffic and Parking, Department of (Box 84, Folder 1532)
    - Tribute to Richard C. Lee (Box 85, Folder 1533)
    - "U" general (Box 85, Folder 1534)
    - United States Conference of Mayors (Box 85, Folder 1535)
    - United State Government (Box 85, Folder 1536)
    - "V" general (Box 85, Folder 1537)
    - "W" general (Box 85, Folder 1538-1539)
    - Welfare (Box 85, Folder 1540)
    - "XYZ" general (Box 85, Folder 1541)
    - Yale University (Box 85, Folder 1542)
  - 1967
    - "A" general (Box 85, Folder 1543)
    - Air pollution (Box 85, Folder 1544)
    - Airport (Box 85, Folder 1545)
    - "B" general (Ba) (Box 85, Folder 1546)
    - "B" general (Be-By) (Box 86, Folder 1547-1549)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant, Board of Directors (Box 86, Folder 1550)
    - Belford, Richard (Box 85, Folder 1551)
    - Bove, Anthony (Box 86, Folder 1552)
    - Burt Laboratory (Box 86, Folder 1553)
    - "C" general (Box 86, Folder 1554-1557)
    - Community Progress, Inc. (Box 87, Folder 1558)
    - Coliseum (Box 87, Folder 1559)
    - Connecticut, State of: general (Box 87, Folder 1560)
    - Connecticut, State of: Highway Department (Box 87, Folder 1561)
    - Connecticut, State of: Highway Department, Route 34 (Box 87, Folder 1562)
    - Corporation Counsel (Box 87, Folder 1563)
    - Curfew proclamations (Box 87, Folder 1564)
    - "D" general (Box 87, Folder 1565-1567)
    - Democratic Party (Box 87, Folder 1568)
    - Dempsey, John N. (Box 87, Folder 1569)
    - Disturbance (Box 87, Folder 1570)
    - "E" general (Box 87, Folder 1571)
    - Education, Department of (Box 87, Folder 1572)
    - "F" general (Box 88, Folder 1573-1574)
    - Finance, Board of (Box 88, Folder 1575)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 88, Folder 1576)
    - "G" general (Box 88, Folder 1577-1578)
    - Gilbert, A. C. Company (Box 88, Folder 1579)
    - Golden, John M. (Box 88, Folder 1580)
    - "H" general (Box 88, Folder 1581-1582)
    - Health, Board of (Box 88, Folder 1583)
    - Herder Report (Box 88, Folder 1584)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Department of (Box 88, Folder 1585)
    - "I" general (Box 88, Folder 1586)
    - "J" general (Box 89, Folder 1587)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B. (Box 89, Folder 1588)
    - "K" general (Box 89, Folder 1589-1591)
    - Klein: eulogy (Box 89, Folder 1592)
    - Knott, Lawson-General Services Administration (Box 89, Folder 1593)
    - "L" general (Box 89, Folder 1594-1596)
    - "Mac" general (Box 89, Folder 1597)
    - "M" general (Box 90, Folder 1598)
    - "N" general (Box 90, Folder 1600)
    - "P" general (Box 90, Folder 1601)
    - Park Department (Box 90, Folder 1602)
    - Public Works, Department of (Box 90, Folder 1603)
    - "Q" general (Box 90, Folder 1604)
    - "R" general (Box 90, Folder 1605-1608)
    - Redevelopment: Adams, Melvin J. (Box 90, Folder 1609)
    - Redevelopment: Adams, Melvin J. (Box 91, Folder 1610)
    - Redevelopment: Court House Complex (Box 91, Folder 1611)
    - Redevelopment: Hill (Box 91, Folder 1612)
    - Redevelopment: Knights of Columbus (Box 91, Folder 1613)
    - Redevelopment: Long Wharf (Box 91, Folder 1614)
    - Redevelopment: miscellaneous (Box 91, Folder 1615-1616)
    - Redevelopment: Wooster Square (Box 91, Folder 1617)
    - Rees, William (Box 91, Folder 1618)
    - Ribicoff, Abraham A. (Box 91, Folder 1619)
    - "S" general (Sa-Sp) (Box 91, Folder 1620-1623)
    - "S" general (St-Sy) (Box 92, Folder 1624)
    - "T" general (Box 92, Folder 1625-1626)
    - Traffic and Parking, Department of (Box 92, Folder 1627)
    - "U" general (Box 92, Folder 1628)
    - United States Government: general (Box 92, Folder 1629)
    - "V" general (Box 92, Folder 1630)
    - "W" general (Box 92, Folder 1631-1633)
    - Welfare (Box 92, Folder 1634)
    - Wires (Box 93, Folder 1635)
    - "XYZ" general (Box 93, Folder 1636)
    - Yale University (Box 93, Folder 1637)
  - 1968
    - "A" general (Box 93, Folder 1638-1639)
    - Administration (Box 93, Folder 1640)
    - Airport (Box 93, Folder 1641)
    - Aldermen, Board of (Box 93, Folder 1642)
    - American Institute of Architects (Box 93, Folder 1643)
    - Arts Center (Box 93, Folder 1644)
    - Assessor (Box 93, Folder 1645)
    - "B" general (Box 93, Folder 1646-1647)
    - Black coalition (Box 93, Folder 1648)
    - Boston Celtics (Box 93, Folder 1649)
    - Building Department (Box 93, Folder 1650)
    - "C" general (Ca-Cl) (Box 93, Folder 1651)
    - "C" general (Co-Cu) (Box 94, Folder 1652)
    - Charter (Box 94, Folder 1653)
    - Citizens Action Commission (Box 94, Folder 1654)
    - City Plan (Box 94, Folder 1655)
    - Coliseum (Box 94, Folder 1656)
    - Community Progress, Inc. (Box 94, Folder 1657)
    - Connecticut, State of: general (Box 94, Folder 1658)
    - Connecticut, State of: Highway Department (Box 94, Folder 1659)
    - Controller (Box 94, Folder 1660)
    - Corporation Counsel (Box 94, Folder 1661-1663)
    - "D" general (Box 94, Folder 1664)
    - Democratic Party (Box 94, Folder 1665)
    - Dempsey, John N. (Box 94, Folder 1666)
    - Development Administrator: Adams, Melvin J. (Box 94, Folder 1667-1668)
    - "E" general (Box 95, Folder 1669)
    - Education, Department of (Box 95, Folder 1670-1671)
    - "F" general (Box 95, Folder 1672-1674)
    - "G" general (Box 95, Folder 1675-1677)
    - Gun Control (Box 95, Folder 1678)
    - Golden, John M. (Box 95, Folder 1679)
    - "H" general (Box 95, Folder 1680)
    - Health, Department of (Box 95, Folder 1681)
    - Hill projects (Box 95, Folder 1682)
    - Housing (Box 95, Folder 1683-1684)
    - Housing and Urban Development (Box 95, Folder 1685)
    - "I" general (Box 95, Folder 1686)
    - "J" general (Box 95, Folder 1687-1688)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B. (Box 95, Folder 1689)
    - "K" general (Box 95, Folder 1690-1692)
    - "L" general (La) (Box 95, Folder 1693)
    - "L" general (Le-Ly) (Box 96, Folder 1694-1697)
    - "M" general (Box 96, Folder 1698-1699)
    - Model Cities Grant (Box 96, Folder 1700)
    - "N" general (Box 96, Folder 1701-1702)
    - New Haven Railroad (Box 96, Folder 1703)
    - "O" general (Box 96, Folder 1704)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity (Box 96, Folder 1705)
    - "P" general (Box 96, Folder 1706-1708)
    - Parks and Recreation (Box 96, Folder 1709)
    - Personnel (Box 96, Folder 1710)
    - Police (Box 96, Folder 1711)
    - Police: Urban Violence (Box 96, Folder 1712)
    - Public Works Department (Box 96, Folder 1713)
    - Purchasing Department (Box 96, Folder 1714)
    - "Q" general (Box 96, Folder 1715)
    - "R" general (Box 96, Folder 1716)
    - Redevelopment (Box 96, Folder 1717)
    - Redevelopment: miscellaneous (Box 96, Folder 1718)
    - Redevelopment; Wooster Square (Box 96, Folder 1719)
    - "S" general (Box 96, Folder 1720)
    - School Disturbances (Box 97, Folder 1721-1722)
    - Traffic and Parking, Department of (Box 97, Folder 1723-1724)
    - "U" general (Box 97, Folder 1725)
    - Unions (Box 97, Folder 1726)
    - United States Government; general (Box 97, Folder 1727)
    - United States Conference of Mayors (Box 97, Folder 1728)
    - "Y" general (Box 97, Folder 1729)
    - Welfare (Box 97, Folder 1730)
    - Whalley Avenue Jail (Box 97, Folder 1731)
    - Yale University (Box 97, Folder 1732-1733)
  - 1969
    - "A" general (Box 97, Folder 1734-1735)
    - Adams, Melvin J. (Box 97, Folder 1736)
    - Administration (Box 97, Folder 1737-1738)
    - Airport (Box 97, Folder 1739)
    - Aldermen, Board of (Box 97, Folder 1740)
    - American Institute of Architects (Box 97, Folder 1741)
    - Arts (Box 97, Folder 1742)
    - Assessors, Board of (Box 97, Folder 1743)
    - "B" general (Ba-Be) (Box 97, Folder 1744-1746)
    - "B" general (Bi-Bu) (Box 98, Folder 1747-1748)
    - Building Department (Box 98, Folder 1749)
    - "C" general (Box 98, Folder 1750-1753)
    - Cappa campaign (Box 98, Folder 1754)
    - Citizens Action Commission (Box 98, Folder 1755)
    - Christmas cards (Box 98, Folder 1756-1757)
    - City Employees' Retirement Board (Box 98, Folder 1758)
    - City Plan (Community Development Action Plan) (Box 98, Folder 1759)
    - Civil Service Commission (Box 98, Folder 1760)
    - Community Progress, Inc. (Box 98, Folder 1761)
    - Connecticut, State of: general (Box 99, Folder 1762)
    - Connecticut, State of: Highway Department (Box 99, Folder 1763)
    - Connecticut, State of: Highway Department Route 34 (Box 99, Folder 1764)
    - Connecticut, State of: proposal new revenues (Box 99, Folder 1765)
    - Controller (Box 99, Folder 1766)
    - Consultants (Box 99, Folder 1767)
    - Corporation Counsel (Box 99, Folder 1768-1769)
    - Counsel of Economic Advisors (Box 99, Folder 1770)
    - "D" general (Box 99, Folder 1771)
    - Democratic Party (Box 99, Folder 1772)
    - Dempsey, John N. (Box 99, Folder 1773)
    - Development Administrator (Box 99, Folder 1774)
    - Dixwell (Box 99, Folder 1775)
    - "E" general (Box 99, Folder 1776)
    - Education, Department of (Box 99, Folder 1777-1778)
    - Equal Opportunity Commission (Box 99, Folder 1779)
    - Ethics, Board of (Box 99, Folder 1780)
    - "F" general (Box 99, Folder 1781-1782)
    - Finance, Board of (Box 100, Folder 1783)
    - Fire Department (Box 100, Folder 1784)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 100, Folder 1785)
    - "G" general (Box 100, Folder 1786-1787)
    - Golden, John M. (Box 100, Folder 1788)
    - Gun control (Box 100, Folder 1789)
    - "H" general (Box 100, Folder 1790-1793)
    - Harper's Magazine (Box 100, Folder 1794)
    - Health, Department of (Box 100, Folder 1795)
    - Hill neighborhood (Box 100, Folder 1796)
    - Homemaker Services Bureau (Box 100, Folder 1797)
    - Housing and Urban Development (Box 100, Folder 1798)
    - Human Relations Council (Box 100, Folder 1799)
    - "I" general (Box 100, Folder 1800)
    - "J" general (Box 100, Folder 1801)
    - "K" general (Box 100, Folder 1801-1803)
    - Knights of Columbus (Box 101, Folder 1804)
    - "L" general (Box 101, Folder 1805-1806)
    - Lee, Richard C.: analysis of (Box 101, Folder 1807)
    - Lee, Richard C.: future plans (Box 101, Folder 1808)
    - Lee Richard C.: personal (Box 101, Folder 1809)
    - Lee Richard C.: tribute (Box 101, Folder 1810)
    - Long Wharf (Box 101, Folder 1811)
    - "M" general (Box 101, Folder 1812-1814)
    - Morra, Marion (Box 101, Folder 1815)
    - Municipal Information System (IBM) (Box 101, Folder 1816)
    - "N" general (Box 101, Folder 1817)
    - National Football Foundation and Hall of Fame (Box 101, Folder 1818)
    - New Haven Register (Box 101, Folder 1819)
    - Noise Pollution (Box 101, Folder 1820)
    - "O" general (Box 101, Folder 1821)
    - Overview (Box 101, Folder 1822)
    - "P" general (Box 101, Folder 1823-1824)
    - Park Board (Box 102, Folder 1825)
    - Park Department (Box 102, Folder 1826)
    - Parks and Recreation Department (Box 102, Folder 1827)
    - Personnel (Box 102, Folder 1828)
    - Police (Box 102, Folder 1829-1830)
    - Police Department - Board of Finance (Box 102, Folder 1831)
    - Police Department: State Planning Committee on Criminal Administration (Box 102, Folder 1832)
    - Political analysis (Box 102, Folder 1833)
    - Portraits (Box 102, Folder 1834)
    - Postal Reform, Citizens Committee for (Box 102, Folder 1835)
    - Press clippings (Box 102, Folder 1836)
    - Public Works (Box 102, Folder 1837)
    - Public Works Department (Box 102, Folder 1838)
    - Public Works: incinerator (Box 102, Folder 1839)
    - "Q" general (Box 102, Folder 1840)
    - Questionnaires (Box 102, Folder 1841)
    - "R" general (Box 102, Folder 1842-1843)
    - Recommendations: college (Box 103, Folder 1844)
    - Recommendations: jobs (Box 103, Folder 1845)
    - Redevelopment (Box 103, Folder 1846)
    - Redevelopment: Adams, Melvin J. (Box 103, Folder 1847)
    - Redevelopment: Architects (Box 103, Folder 1848)
    - Redevelopment: city demonstration (Box 103, Folder 1849)
    - Redevelopment: Coliseum (Box 103, Folder 1850-1852)
    - Redevelopment: Cramer, Richard (Box 103, Folder 1853)
    - Redevelopment: Crown Street Garage (Box 103, Folder 1854)
    - Redevelopment: Dixwell Project (Box 103, Folder 1855)
    - Redevelopment: Fair Haven Project (Box 103, Folder 1856)
    - Redevelopment: Hill (Box 103, Folder 1857)
    - Redevelopment: Holt, Phillip (Box 103, Folder 1858)
    - Redevelopment: Knights of Columbus (Box 103, Folder 1859)
    - Redevelopment: miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 1860)
    - Redevelopment; Newhallville Project (Box 103, Folder 1861)
    - Redevelopment: other cities (Box 103, Folder 1862)
    - Redevelopment: relocation, housing (Box 103, Folder 1863)
    - Redevelopment: Armstrong, Roger (Box 103, Folder 1864)
    - Redevelopment: Wooster Square (Box 103, Folder 1865)
    - Redevelopment Agency: model cities (Box 103, Folder 1866)
    - Redevelopment Agency: petitions (Box 103, Folder 1867)
    - Redevelopment Agency: Shannon, Charles I. (Box 103, Folder 1868)
    - Redevelopment Agency: Susnoff, Eugene N. (Box 104, Folder 1869)
    - Regional groups (Mutual Police Assistance Compact, etc.) (Box 104, Folder 1870)
    - Registrar of Voters (Box 104, Folder 1871)
    - Ribicoff, Abraham A. (Box 104, Folder 1872)
    - "S" general (Box 104, Folder 1873-1875)
    - South Central Community College (Box 104, Folder 1876)
    - Southern Connecticut State College (Box 104, Folder 1877)
    - "T" general (Box 104, Folder 1878)
    - Tax Department (Box 104, Folder 1879)
    - Tax Exempt Committee (Box 104, Folder 1880)
    - Tax Review, Board of (Box 104, Folder 1881)
    - Television, radio (Box 104, Folder 1882)
    - Traffic and Parking, Department of (Box 104, Folder 1883)
    - "U" general (Box 105, Folder 1884)
    - Unions (Box 105, Folder 1885)
    - University of Florida (Box 105, Folder 1886)
    - Urban America (Box 105, Folder 1887)
    - Urban renewal (Box 105, Folder 1888)
    - Urban Violence (Box 105, Folder 1889)
    - "V" general (Box 105, Folder 1890)
    - Vietnam (Pueblo) (Box 105, Folder 1891)
    - "W" general (Box 105, Folder 1892-1893)
    - Welfare (Box 105, Folder 1894)
    - Welfare Island (Box 105, Folder 1895)
    - Whalley Avenue Jail (Box 105, Folder 1896)
    - White House correspondence (Box 105, Folder 1897)
    - "XYZ" general (Box 105, Folder 1899)
    - Yale University (Box 106, Folder 1900-1901)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 106, Folder 1902)
- Subject Files, 1934-1969; Series II; 3.75 linear feet (9 boxes)
  This series was established by the mayor's office to bring together material on important individuals and subjects.
  The files are arranged alphabetically by subject or person and then chronologically within each folder. The series contains little on such important subjects on redevelopment, urban planning, the war on poverty, and town-town relations, but does provide useful information of a biographical nature on Richard C. Lee, some material on race relations, and a significant amount of documentation on New Haven and Connecticut politics. Many of the people and subjects in Series II can also be found in Series I under the name of the person, subject, and/or in the "Letter" general files. Researchers, therefore, should examine both Series I and II for relevant material.
  Those interested in biograhpical material on Lee should examine Box 111, folders 1993-1995. For information about civil rights, researchers should consult such files as those on Black Muslims, NAACP, Negro participation, Riots, and Sit-outs. Connecticut and New Haven politics, together with Lee's relationship with leading politicians, are discussed in such files as those established for William Benton, Joseph Einhorn, Robert N. Giaimo, John M. Golden and Grapevine Press.
  - Aberdeen Fund, 1962, 1963 (Box 107, Folder 1903)
  - Amerling Company, 1962 (Box 107, Folder 1904)
  - Adley, 1961 (Box 107, Folder 1905)
  - Assessment, 1954-1959 (Box 107, Folder 1906)
  - B. Altman and Company, 1963 (Box 107, Folder 1907)
  - Bailey, John M., 1953-1969 (Box 107, Folder 1908)
  - Bank Officers, 1963-1965 (Box 107, Folder 1909)
  - Barbarito, A. Mark, 1955-1956 (Box 107, Folder 1910)
  - Barber, John (NAACP), undated (Box 107, Folder 1911)
  - Barbieri, Arthur T., 1957, 1965 (Box 107, Folder 1912)
  - Belford, Richard, 1962 (Box 107, Folder 1913)
  - Benton, William, 1953-1969 (Box 107, Folder 1914-1915)
  - Bibliography of Articles about New Haven, 1964 (Box 107, Folder 1916)
  - Black Muslims, 1963 (Box 107, Folder 1917)
  - Blake, Priestley, 1964 (Box 107, Folder 1918)
  - Bonwit Teller, 1966, 1967 (Box 107, Folder 1919)
  - Bowles, Chester, 1949-1958 (Box 107, Folder 1920)
  - Brewster, Kingman, 1964, 1965 (Box 107, Folder 1921)
  - Bush, Prescott, 1955-1961 (Box 107, Folder 1922-1926)
  - Carnegie Corporation, 1969 (Box 107, Folder 1927)
  - Celentano, William C., 1946-[1964?] (Box 107, Folder 1928)
  - Crawford, George W., 1955-1966 (Box 107, Folder 1929)
  - Christmas cards (sent), 1954-1968 (Box 107, Folder 1930-1931)
  - Christmas cards (received), 1957-1968, undated (Box 108, Folder 1932)
  - Church Street Project, 1959-1963 (Box 108, Folder 1933)
  - Dahl, Robert: "Who Governs", 1959-1963 (Box 108, Folder 1934)
  - Damiani, B. Fred, 1955, 1957 (Box 108, Folder 1935)
  - Davenport, James, 1960-1963 (Box 108, Folder 1936-1938)
  - Democratic Party Rules and Regulations, 1957 (Box 108, Folder 1939)
  - Dempsey, John N., 1961-1963 (Box 108, Folder 1940)
  - DePalma, Michael re: Fire Department, undated (Box 108, Folder 1941)
  - DeVit, George, 1955-1964 (Box 108, Folder 1942)
  - DeVita, Henry, 1955-[1965?] (Box 108, Folder 1943)
  - DiBenedetto, Alphonse, 1957-1959, undated (Box 108, Folder 1944)
  - DiCenzo, George, 1955-1958 (Box 108, Folder 1945)
  - DiSesa, Joseph, 1963-1964 (Box 108, Folder 1946)